This whole process of embryonic flexion, not
胚の屈曲の全過程は、単に
only organizes the placement of my joints,
関節の配置を組織するだけでなく、
but also begins to cause a phase of embryonic delimitation.
胚の境界形成の段階を引き起こし始めます。
A set of four embryonic structures.
4つの胚性構造の集合体です。
There are four embryonic structures.
4つの胚性構造があります。
These four structures are the septum transversum, the
これら4つの構造は、横中隔、
pleural membranes,
胸膜、
peritoneal, the
腹膜、
paraxial mesoblast of the
幹壁の軸傍中胚葉、
trunk wall and the
および
esophageal mesenchyme.
食道間葉です。
Beyond the prechordal
前索板の向こう側、
plate, in the cephalic
頭部領域で、
region, the mesenchymal
胚盤の間葉系細胞が
cells of the embryonic disc
心膜となり、
will become the pericardium
横中隔となります。
and the septum transversum.
これは脊索です。
This is the notochord.
傍索とは、
Parachordal means
横に、という意味です。
next to.
前索、
Prechordal,
そこを意味し、前索板の向こう側、つまりここ、
that means there and beyond the prechordal plate, that is, here, in
頭部領域で、間葉系細胞、その
the cephalic region, the mesenchymal cells, the
そこにある間葉の細胞、
mesenchymal cells, which are there, of the
胚盤の細胞が、
embryonic disc, will become
心膜および横中隔となります。
the pericardium and the septum transversum.
言い換えれば、
In other words,
あなたの心臓はすでに頭の上で発達しているだけでなく、
Not only is your heart already developing above your head,
しかし、これをどのように説明できるでしょうか？
but how can we explain that?
それがこの動きをするという事実によってです。
By the fact that it makes that movement.
Par le fait que ça fait ce mouvement-là.
That is, they are already in place, in fact.
つまり、それらは実際にはすでに適切な位置にあるのです。
They are already there.
それらはすでにそこにあります。
And this is very important because it's something that,
そして、これは非常に重要です。なぜなら、これは、
in classical embryology, we don't see it.
古典的な発生学では見られないことだからです。
We describe the movement of the heart, you see?
心臓の動きを記述しますよね？
It descends, but no, it doesn't descend, it's the other one that goes up, you see
それは下降すると言われますが、いいえ、下降するのではなく、他のものが上昇するのです、分かりますか？
?
腎臓についても同様で、腎臓の上昇が記述されますが、いいえ、腎臓はその場に留まり、他のものが下降するのです。
Same thing with the kidneys, we describe the ascent of the joint, but no, the kidney stays
私がこのフレーズを聞くとすぐにピンときます。それは、心膜と横隔膜が機能的な単位であるということを意味します。
in place, it's the rest that descends.
そして、心臓を研究する際に、その律動性が、
When I hear that sentence, it immediately clicks, it means that the pericardium and
心膜筋膜によって支持されている心臓の。言い換えれば、もし私が取り除くと、
your diaphragm are a functional unit,
電気だけでは、
and we will see that when we study the heart, we will see that the rhythmicity,
心臓の電気だけでは維持するのに十分ではなく、振動システムがあり、
of the heart is supported by the pericardial fascia. In other words, if I remove
閉じた、ほとんど～のような、
that the electricity
かなり素晴らしいエネルギーが心膜内で生じ、
alone of the heart is not enough to maintain it and that there is a closed oscillation system,
その律動性において心臓を支持しているのです。
almost like
さらに、それは心臓と完全に連結しており、
a rather brilliant energy, which occurs in the pericardium to support the
横隔膜の間で連結しています。
heart in its rhythmicity.
これらは二つの別々のものなのではなく、最初はほとんど同じ細胞が組織化されていくのです。
And moreover, it is completely connected between the heart
それが上の方に見られ、そしてそのようになり、このようにしてここに統合されているのが分かります。
and the diaphragm.
ここにある心膜のレベルと、
They are not two separate things, they are initially almost the same cells that will organize themselves.
そこにある横中隔のレベルで、同時に統合されています。
We see that it is found up there, then it does that, that's
したがって、屈曲、脊索は、
how they are integrated here,
私の神経管のレベルで特定の動きを引き起こし、それがさらに、
both at the level of the pericardium which is here, and
神経溝の動きを引き起こし、それが、
the septum transversum which is there.
側方構造を小血管へと組織化し、それが供給源となりますが、
So the flexion, the notochord causes a
栄養的なものでありながら、発達による相対的な成長の抑制ともなります。
specific movement at the level of my neural tube which in turn will cause a
mouvement  spécifique  au  niveau  de  mon  tube  neural  qui  lui  va  entraîner  un
neural groove movement which organizes the
mouvement  de  gouttière  neural  qui  organise  la
lateral structure into small vessels that become a nutritional
structure  latérale  en  petit  vaisseau  qui  devienne  un  apport
supply but a relative brake on growth due to the very important
nutritif  mais  un  frein  pour  la  croissance  relatif  par  le  développement
development of my neural tube.
私の神経管にとって非常に重要です。
the ectoderm around that rolls up and in this rolling movement,
周囲の外胚葉が巻き込み、この巻き込み運動の中で、
we're already going to imagine that the cells are there, you see, here.
細胞がここに、ほら、あるとすでに想像してみましょう。
Well, they come to do that, so it doesn't move, it does that.
ええと、それらはこのように動きます。だから、それは動かず、このようにします。
And that's how these mesenchymal cells come to integrate
そして、このようにしてこれらの間葉系細胞が統合されます。
to form the future pericardial tissue and form the diaphragmatic anlage.
将来の心膜組織を形成し、横隔膜原基を形成するために。
It brings cells that will develop around.
それは周囲に発達する細胞をもたらします。
All this grows and at some point, my visit...
これらすべてが成長し、ある時点で、私の卵黄茎は...
The vitelline pedicle no longer grows. It has finished its job.
卵黄茎はもはや成長しません。その役割を終えました。
It's just a small remnant that inserts with vitelline vessels
それは卵黄血管とともに挿入される小さな残存物にすぎません。
around what we call the umbilical region with the umbilical networks.
臍血管網とともに、いわゆる臍帯部の周囲に。
The vesicle will be integrated into the pedicle to form the umbilical cord
卵黄嚢は茎に統合され、臍帯を形成します。
and the pericardium will integrate with the septum transversum to form this tissue
そして心膜は横中隔と統合され、この組織を形成します。
whose origin is initially beyond the prechordal plate.
その起源は最初、前脊索板の向こう側にあります。
We see here the septum transversum, you see, which is here, which
ここに見えるのは横中隔です、ほら、ここにあるのが。
is an important tissue.
重要な組織です。
We will see that there is growth.
成長があることがわかります。
Initially, the septum transversum is there, you see, at the fourth
最初、横中隔は、ほら、第4週にはそこにあります。
week.
週です。
Then at the fifth week, it horizontalizes, you
そして第5週には、それは水平になります、ほら。
see, and then it starts to descend, here, like that.
ほら、そしてここでこのように下降し始めます。
But in fact, look, it comes here, and then it descends completely.
しかし実際には、ご覧ください、それはここに来て、完全に下降します。
like that. So, what does that mean? Initially, it has its origin
このように。では、それは何を意味するのでしょうか？最初、その起源は
when it is
それが
2 mm, it originates at the very high cervical vertebrae. C3,
2 mmの時、それは非常に高い頸椎レベル、C3にその起源を持ちます。
C4, which is the origin
C4、それは起源である。
of the phrenic nerve. And then, it
ちょうど横隔神経の。そして、それは
ends up at the lumbar level,
最終的には腰椎レベルで見られます。
by pulling here. What is this drawing in
ここで引き起こしながら。この図は
biodynamics?
バイオダイナミクスにおいて何を意味するのでしょうか？
is wrong. Why?
それは間違いです。なぜか？
Because it makes it descend, whereas it's...
なぜなら、それは下降させるからです。しかし実際は...
It's the rest that comes. Exactly. This is the image of the
残りの部分が来るのです。その通りです。これは、
train leaving. I think I'm moving, but in fact, I haven't moved.
出発する列車のイメージです。私は動いていると思っても、実際には動いていないのです。
The truth is that this becomes a fulcrum
真実は、これが支点となり、
and it's all the rest around that has dislocated.
そして周囲の他の全てが移動したということです。
Do you understand the idea?
この考えが理解できますか？
So the diaphragm, it settles, it positions itself, and I have enormous growth
つまり、横隔膜は定着し、位置を定め、そしてその周囲に巨大な成長が起こります。
around,
周囲に、
and it is this growth of the posterior part, you see here, 1, then
そして、この後方部分の成長です。ここを見てください、1、そして
the growth, 2, the embryo actually grows, you see,
成長、2、実際には胚が成長しているのです、分かりますか、
and it creates a, in fact it will even create an absorption space here, as
そしてそれは、実際にはここに吸収空間を作り出します。なぜなら
it grows, it will create a space here, you see, between there, and there I have a space
それが成長するにつれて、ここに空間が生まれます、分かりますか、ここからここまでの間に空間が
that opens here.
ここに開くのです。
And what will be attracted there, into that space?
そして、この空間に何が引き寄せられるでしょうか？
My lungs, which are a suction field as we will discuss,
私の肺です。それは、後で話すように吸引場となるものです。
which will be aspirated here, here, which we will see in phase 2, at the
それがここに、ここに吸引されます。これはフェーズ2、すなわち
viscerocranium.
内臓頭蓋（viscérocrâne）で見るでしょう。
The diaphragmatic origin is found very, very high,
横隔膜の発生源は非常に高い位置にあります。
it is found at the level of the second and third cervical vertebrae.
第2および第3頸椎のレベルに位置します。
But it's all the part above.
しかし、成長するのはその上部全体です。
that grows. So the nerve
が成長するのです。したがって、神経は
is not pulled like that,
このように引っ張られるのではなく、
but it's almost pulled like that.
むしろこのように引っ張られるのです。
We see this setup
この配置が見られます。
of this diaphragm
この横隔膜の
linked with
と関連して
this excessive growth
この過剰な成長が
that we will see, that we will study tomorrow
見られるでしょう、明日詳細に研究する
in detail, why the embryo
なぜ胚が
at some point, it stops
ある時点で、それは止まります。
in its flexion.
その屈曲において。
The embryo straightens up. Why
胚はまっすぐになります。なぜ
does it straighten up? What happens?
まっすぐになるのですか？何が起こっているのですか？
It's a question of fluids on the sclerotome.
これは硬化組織（sclerotome）上の体液の問題です。
with the straightening of the telencephalon.
終脳の伸展を伴って。
The ascent of my neural tube and the descent of my digestive system.
私の神経管の上昇と消化器系の下降。
This is what will create this space here, the integration.
これがここの空間、統合を生み出します。
Here we can clearly see on a section the different tissues, septum transversum,
ここでは、横隔中隔（septum transversum）など、さまざまな組織が断面でよく見えます。
the pleuroperitoneal membranes and also what we call the meso-esophageal
胸膜腹膜膜（pleuroperitoneal membranes）と、いわゆる中隔（meso）も
and the paraxial membranes that are there.
食道間膜（mesoesophagus）
Not only working on a diaphragm means working on all these spaces
横隔膜を治療することは、これらすべての空間を治療することだけでなく
here.
ここで。
Often, we work on them here.
しばしば、私たちはここでそれらを治療します。
But in fact, working on a diaphragm is not only freeing all this,
しかし実際には、横隔膜を治療することは、これらすべてを解放するだけでなく、
these lateral spaces, but also the aorta, the
これらの側方空間だけでなく、大動脈（aorta）、
vena cava and the esophagus,
大静脈（vena cava）、そして食道（esophagus）も
and especially the esophageal junction.
そして特に食道接合部（esophageal junction）。
Because it's a very important area to free up a diaphragm.
なぜなら、横隔膜を解放するために非常に重要な領域だからです。
Many patients suffer from...
多くの患者が...に苦しんでいます。
esophagitis, peptic disorders
食道炎（esophagitis）、消化性潰瘍（peptic disorders）
in the esophagus, enormously.
食道のレベルで、非常に多く。
Well, that blocks your diaphragm.
ええと、それはあなたの横隔膜をブロックします。
It is absolutely necessary to free and clear
絶対に解放し、クリアにする必要があります
this peri-esophageal space
この食道周囲空間（peri-esophageal space）を
with the muscle of Treitz,
トライツ筋（Treitz's muscle）と共に、
the muscle of Anscouver,
アンカヴァー筋（Anscouver's muscle）と共に、
this small peri-esophageal space
この小さな食道周囲空間
which can even block the entire digestive system
それは消化器系全体さえもブロックする可能性があります
which is suspended vis-à-vis the carotid foramina,
頸動脈管に対して懸垂している、
vis-à-vis the prejugular system,
前頸静脈系に対して、
vis-à-vis of...
〜に対して…
of your anterior, posterior pterygoid attachments,
あなたの翼突筋の前方、後方の付着部に対して、
at the base of the skull, inferior part,
頭蓋底の下部において、
which can create everything here, it's supported.
ここで全てを生み出すことができ、それは支持されています。
And so, if you don't have the bell ringing in your head
ですから、もし頭の中で「ビン」と鐘が鳴るような感覚がなければ、
when it goes down here,
ここが下降する時、
you are not free on your symphysis.
あなたのシンフィシスは自由ではありません。
Because in fact, what happens here?
なぜなら実際、ここで何が起こっているのでしょうか？
You have a magical continuity,
あなたには魔法のような連続性があります、
with a small muscle that is a muscle
ある小さな筋肉と共に、それは筋肉であり、
which for me is the magician of the system...
私にとってシステムの魔術師である…
of sphincter opening,
括約筋の開放、
of organizing all
全ての組織化、
the functional integrity
機能的完全性、
of your primitive vegetative system
あなたの原始的な自律神経系、
and even current
そして現在のものさえも、
in relation to that.
それと関連しています。
And what is it called? It continues here.
そしてそれは何と呼ばれますか？それはここで続いています。
Look, it does this
ご覧ください、それはこれを行い、
and it continues there. What is that called?
そしてそこで続いています。これは何と呼ばれますか？
The muscle of Treitz.
搾り出し筋です。
Which contains two types of fibers. Muscle
それは2種類の線維を含んでいます。線維は、
and non-muscle fibers.
筋線維と非筋線維です。
So two different types of information.
つまり、2種類の異なる情報です。
it's a muscle that can open
それは開くことができる筋肉であり、
or close the air care
または気道の括約筋を閉じることもできます。
the falciform ligament, the greater omentum
鎌状間膜、大網は、
are derived elements
派生要素です。
of the septum transversum
横中隔から
so what can we say?
では、何が言えるでしょうか？
that 1. I have a continuity
1. 連続性があるということです
not only from my mesenchymal
私の間葉系細胞からだけでなく
cells
間葉系細胞
via the pericardial system
心膜系を介して
and septum transversum
そして横中隔
but that in addition
さらに
from the septum transversum will derive
横中隔からは
a part of my falciform
私の靭帯の一部である
ligament, and at the same time
鎌状靭帯が派生し、同時に
the greater omentum, which are elements
大網も派生します。これらは
that are derived from this transverse septum.
この横中隔から派生した要素です。
And I remind you that the greater omentum
そして、大網は
is part of this
この
functional integrity of the
横隔膜の機能的統合性の一部をなしていることを思い出してください。
diaphragm. I am here,
私はここにいます、
I have the hiatus of Winslow, and I pass
ウィンスロー孔があり、私は
behind the retro-gastric pouch.
胃後嚢の裏側を通過します。
You see? So I go up
分かりますか？それで、私は上がっていきます
towards the area of the
の領域へ
bronchus, I orient my right-left bronchus,
気管支、私の左主気管支を向けます、
I go towards the spleen, and then I go down again,
脾臓へ向かい、そしてまた下がっていきます、
I pass under the
の下を通り、
above the colon,
結腸の上を、
and I go down again to form
そして、私は再び下がって
a coalescence of four layers
4枚の葉の合着を形成し、
to form a greater omentum.
大網を形成します。
Lymphatic messenger,
リンパメッセンジャー、
B, T and M, motility,
B細胞、T細胞、M細胞、運動性、
in relation, all that,
これらすべてが関連しており、
with my diaphragmatic system.
私の横隔膜系と。
Another important thing,
もう一つ重要なことは、
is this relationship, you see,
この関係です、ご覧の通り、
with what we call the arcuate ligaments.
いわゆる弓状靭帯との。
You know that, they are here, you see.
ご存知でしょう、それらはここにあります、ご覧の通り。
It's the arcuate ligament,
それは弓状靭帯、
arched ligament,
弓状靭帯であり、
with the psoas arch,
大腰筋弓との関係です。
the median arcuate ligament
内側弓状靭帯は、
with the aortic hiatus.
大動脈裂孔と。
And above, you have an important passage,
そしてその上には、重要な通路があります、
this continuity with the ligament of Treitz.
連結靭帯とのこの連続性です。
But this is interesting
しかし、これは興味深い、
because this is an arcuate ligament
なぜなら、これは弓状靭帯であり、
with the quadratus lumborum.
腰方形筋との関係です。
The medial arcuate ligament
内側弓状靭帯は、
with the psoas arch.
大腰筋弓との関係です。
That means the diaphragm
それはつまり、横隔膜が
continues indirectly
間接的に連続しているということです、
through my common masses,
私の脊柱起立筋群の共通腱を介して、
through my quadratus lumborum up to here,
私の腰方形筋を介してここまで、
and even up to here vis-à-vis my psoas.
そしてさらに、私の大腰筋と関連してここまで。
They are in direct relation with my diaphragm.
それらは私の横隔膜と直接関係しています。
It's a fascial continuity
これは筋膜の連続性であり、
of diaphragmatic organization.
横隔膜の組織化におけるものです。
And how can esophagitis disturb
そして、食道の問題がどのように乱すことができるか、
even the movement of the knee, for example,
例えば、膝の動きさえも、
by disturbing your mechanics.
あなたの力学を乱すことによって。
Each diaphragm
各横隔膜は
to conceive it as in
それを～として捉えるために
relation with the other diaphragms.
他の横隔膜との関連で。
Each of the three main diaphragms, cervical, thoracic,
3つの主要な大横隔膜、すなわち頸部、胸部、
pelvic,
骨盤のそれぞれにおいて、
an imbalance of one disturbs the other. Moreover, I find myself in a negative
いずれかの不均衡が他方を乱す。さらに、私は圧力が
pressure
陰圧
with a positive pressure.
陽圧と共にある。
That is, it is a pressure regulator, so it is a tension regulator,
つまり、それは圧力調整器であり、したがって
so it is a hydraulic and even thermal regulator.
張力調整器であり、したがって油圧調整器であり、さらには熱調整器でもある。
You see how this digestive, vascular,
この消化器系、血管系の横隔膜がどのように機能するか、
lymphatic diaphragm, it's a lymphatic pump?
リンパ系、つまりリンパポンプであるか、わかるだろうか？
How all that vis-à-vis, just of its system, vis-à-vis of the
これらすべてが、そのシステム自体に対して、
esophagus, vis-à-vis of the whole system,
食道に対して、システム全体に対して、
cardiac, with its cardiac relation, of all its relation with the phoepatis, and
心臓系に対して、その心臓との関連、肝臓とのあらゆる関連、そして
all its relation
そのあらゆる関連が
posterior with the greater omentum. And behind, we will find all the
大網との後方での関連。そして後方には、
relation with the quadratus lumborum,
腰方形筋とのあらゆる関連、
and in addition with the psoas. But
さらに大腰筋との関連がある。しかし、
all that is the same continuity from the heart, from the esophagus,
これらすべては、心臓から、食道から、
from the base of the skull, so from the craniosacral axis.
頭蓋底から、つまり頭蓋仙骨軸からの一連の連続性である。
whether it is the purely notochordal axis or the purely
それが純粋な脊索軸であろうと、純粋な
Corrings axis.
コリングスの軸であろうと。
The costodiaphragmatic recesses are accumulation sacs for exudates, waste,
肋骨横隔膜陥凹は、滲出液や老廃物の貯留嚢であり、
both exudates, transpleural and transperitoneal. What does this sentence mean? I have bronchitis, I cough, I point my finger, I have small microbes. I have to eliminate these microbes, after they will not remain complicated. They must be eliminated. They pass. That's why very often, when you have pneumonia afterwards, you have blocked lung bases. It's the same thing if you have gastric problems. If you do something like that, you will eliminate. It accumulates. They need one main thing, it's... space.
老廃物である。
it's...
それらは通過します。
space.
そのため、多くの場合、
This is where we see that the human
ここで、身体が
body is a unit at the cellular level, 1, at the tissue level,
人間は細胞レベルで一つの単位であり、組織レベルでも一つの単位であり、
2, and these reactions
そして、これらの
of defense and integration can occur at any level.
防御と統合の反応は、あらゆるレベルで起こり得ます。
Why? Because
なぜか？なぜなら、
there is a tissue continuity of the splanchnopleure and the somatopleure. This
内臓側板（splanchnopleure）と体壁側板（somatopleure）の組織的な連続性があるからです。
is
それは
what we just saw with the diaphragm.
横隔膜で確認したばかりのことです。